<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>medium on Ayan Bag</title>
    <link>https://example.com/tags/medium/</link>
    <description>Recent content in medium on Ayan Bag</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/medium/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to Multi-threading in Python</title>
      <link>https://example.com/articles/intro-to-mutlithreading-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/articles/intro-to-mutlithreading-python/</guid>
      <description>Like multiprocessing, multithreading **is a way of achieving multitasking. Most of the code we write in Python is single threaded. A python virtual machine runs behind the scene uses a thread called the main thread i.e main() to execute the code which has written.
A thread is an entity within a process that can be scheduled for execution. Also, it is the smallest unit of processing that can be performed in an OS (Operating System).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Sweet Introduction to R Programming</title>
      <link>https://example.com/articles/sweet-introduction-to-r-programming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/articles/sweet-introduction-to-r-programming/</guid>
      <description>R is a open source and very popular programming language and environment for statistical computer and graphics.R was designed by statisticians and was specialized for statistical computing, and thus is known as the lingua franca of statistics. It is mostly used in Data Science and Machine Learning. It is managed by R core development team — team of volunteer developer from across the globe. R provide a wide variety of statistical and graphical techniques and highly extensible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Termina Chat Application with Python and Pusher</title>
      <link>https://example.com/articles/building-terminal-chat-application/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/articles/building-terminal-chat-application/</guid>
      <description>It is better to have a conversation
In our daily life we encounter with many chat application which a really awesome. It takes a lot effort to develop and maintain these application because it involves a two way communication between different user and logging each and every request provide by server.
Getting inspired by the chat application as we see in Die Hard 4, I created my own realtime chat application .</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>